Hey. What's the matter?
錢德，你的臉到底是怎麼了？
Somebody on the subway licked my neck! Licked my neck!
-怎麼了？ -搭地鐵時有人舔我的脖子
No, Willie's still alive! What are you guys doing?
喬伊，你在這裡做什麼？
Oh, my mom called. They're going to run our engagement announcement in the local paper,
他們要登報通知親友 我們要訂婚了
so we're looking for a good picture of us. Ooh, I'm afraid that does not exist.
-我們在找一張很漂亮的合照 -恐怕那是不可能的事
That's not true. There are great pictures of us.
我們合拍了很多不錯的照片
No, there are great pictures of you standing next to a guy who's going like this.
不，你照的很好 但你旁邊的男人是這樣的
Oh, my God! That's the creep that you're with at the Statue of Liberty!
天啊，他就是在自由女神像旁 跟你合照的怪胎
I don't know what it is. I just can't take a good picture.
我不知道這是怎麼一回事 我就沒辦法好好照相
Oh, here's a great one. Yeah, I'm not in that.
這一張很不錯
No, but look at me all tan. Hey, why don't you guys go get portraits
沒關係，我們不需要你們 我已經忘了這件事
done by a professional photographer? It's a great idea. I bet they have one of
那是個好點子 我敢說他們一定有大風扇
those wind machines, you know, like... Yeah, that's great. Next to that, Chandler
那的確很棒，真的那麼做的話 錢德應該看起來不會這麼蠢
won't look so stupid. So, Chandler, what do you say?
你沒有聽到 剛剛我說的話嗎？
All right, but I should warn you, I'm not going. I'm going.
你能不能別再跟他一起出去？
Dude, that reverse layup. And how about those three pointers?
-那些三分球呢？ -棒到不行
Amazing. And those guys were this close to letting
這次也是就差這麼一點 那些傢伙就答應讓我們上場了
us play this time, too. Hey, look, look. Phoebe's talking to a cute
你們看 菲比在跟咖啡廳帥哥說話
coffeehouse guy. Oh, you guys call him cute coffeehouse guy?
你叫他「咖啡廳帥哥」嗎？ 我們叫他「邊尿邊哼歌先生」
We call him Humswelly Peas. I guess when we call Ross, lingers in the
對，我們叫羅斯 「浴室裡的思考家」
bathroom. Hey, you guys, Humswelly Peas just asked
大伙們，邊尿邊哼歌先生 剛剛約我出去
me out. Wait, I thought that guy was married.
-我以為他結婚了 -沒錯，但他正在辦離婚
He is, but he's getting divorced. Ross, maybe you know him.
羅斯，或許你認識他
It's not a club. Phoebe, if this guy's going through a divorce,
我就知道你會那麼說
is it such a good idea to start going out with him?
我不是要你跟他約會
Hey, divorced men are not bad men. They have that on the napkins at the club.
-離婚男人不是壞男人 -他們把那句話印在俱樂部的紙巾上
Oh, I gotta get back to work. You don't have to be back for a half hour.
-我得回去上班了 -你還可以休息半小時
Yeah, but my assistant, Tag, does sit-ups in the office during lunch.
我的助理泰格午餐時間時 會在辦公室做仰臥起坐
Oh, I could just spread him on a cracker. If you have a crush on this guy, why would
我真的快被他迷死了
you hire him? I mean, you know you can't date him, right?
-你知道你不能跟他約會，對吧？ -對，我知道
Oh, no, I know that. I know that. Although, we made a joke, though, that we
-對，那一張沒有我 -沒錯，但我全身曬得黑亮
spent so much time together, he should call me his work wife.
我們開玩笑說 因為我們常常在一起 他應該叫我「工作上的太太」
Oh. Soon he'll be able to call you that lady he
很快地他就可以叫你 「那個被開除的女人」
knew that got fired. I'm not gonna get fired because I'm not gonna
我不會被開除 因為我不會採取行動
act on it. So then you wouldn't mind if he was dating
你不會介意 他跟別人約會吧？
someone else? Why, is he? He is, isn't he? He's dating that
怎麼了？他有嗎？他有，對吧？ 他跟行銷部那個蕩婦約會
slut in marketing. Maybe I should open a divorced men's club.
或許我該成立 一個離婚男子俱樂部
Dude, that's so sad. I could put a basketball court in the back.
我會在後院設一個籃球場
Could I play? Oh, no sit-ups today, Tag?
你今天不做仰臥起坐嗎？泰格
I just did them. Oh, well, drop and give me ten more.
-我剛剛做完 -再做十下吧
What? I had a drink with lunch. Did those, um...
我午餐喝了酒
Did those cost reports come in? Yeah, I filled them out last night.
-成本報告送過來了嗎？ -我昨晚就已經歸檔了
Oh, great. Could you make me four copies of those?
麻煩你幫我影印四份
Sure. Great, thank you.
-沒問題 -太棒了，謝謝你
Oh. Hey, Rachel.
-不 -沒錯
Oh, hi. Hi, Alyssa, what's up? I'm just, uh, about to, um, go out to the
我正好要去血拼
store, get some stuff to put in my backpack. You know, like dried fruit
買些東西放進我的背包裡
and granola and stuff like that. Um, what's up?
水果干，速食麥片 大概就是那一類的東西
Is Tag here? No, why?
-有什麼事嗎？ -泰格在嗎？
Oh, well, I was gonna talk to him about doing something tonight.
我要來問他 今晚要不要跟我出去
Really? You got a little crush on Tag there, do ya?
真的嗎？ 你喜歡泰格，對吧？
Yeah, well, we've been flirting back and forth, but I was hoping that
我們一直都在眉來眼去的…
tonight it would turn into something a little more than that.
但我希望今晚 事情能有點進展
Oh, okay, whoa, whoa, easy there, Melissa. This ain't a locker room, okay?
別猴急，梅麗莎 這裡不是更衣室
But, you know, I remember him saying that he had plans tonight.
但我記得他說過 今晚他已經有約了
Oh, no. Oh, yeah.
嘿，太好了，你們兩個都在
All right, back to work.
好吧，快回去工作
Hey, isn't that Tag's backpack?
那不是泰格的背包嗎？
Yeah, Melissa, you know, I don't want to be known as the office bitch,
我不想當辦公室的臭女人 但我會打電話給你主管
but I will call your supervisor.
我會忘記他的
Great. That's great, Monica. Great.
太棒了，非常不錯，摩妮卡
Now, Chandler, you want to give us a smile?
好了，錢德 你能笑一個嗎？
Okay.
好吧
I'm sorry, is the seat uncomfortable?
-對不起，那張椅子很不舒服嗎？ -不，是我很不舒服
No, I am.
布魯克林好遠
Chandler, I know you can do this, okay? You have a beautiful smile.
錢德，我知道你辦得到 你笑起來很帥
I do? Yeah.
-是嗎？ -沒錯
All right, maybe you don't have to smile.
或許你不必笑 我們來試試別的點子
Let's try something else. Let's try, um, try looking sexy.
我知道，我們來試試看…
Okay.
好吧
Stop. Or not.
還是不要吧
Hi, Joey. What are you doing here?
昨晚你做了什麼？
Uh, well, I got an audition down the street,
我要在街底試鏡 結果醬汁沾到衣服上了
and I spilled sauce all over the front of my shirt.
多花一點時間在臥室裡
You got an extra one?
-你有多餘的襯衫嗎？ -當然有
Yeah, sure. Um...
對，有啊
Here.
拿去吧
Great.
太棒了
You got anything that's not Ralph Lauren?
你有除了勞夫羅蘭外 其他品牌的衣服嗎？
Yeah, I don't think so, Joe.
應該沒有，喬伊
All right, I guess this will be fine.
我猜這件應該可以
Hey, listen, uh, what are you doing tonight?
-你今晚要做什麼？ -沒事，怎麼了？
Nothing. Why?
他不在，怎麼了？
How would you feel about taking out my assistant, Tag? I'll pay.
你要不要帶我的助理泰格 出去玩？我付錢
Oh, Rach, I got to say, it's going to take a lot of money
我想我們不會 有那樣的問題…
for me to go out on a date with a dude.
要我跟男人出去約會 可得付我一大筆錢
I'm not asking you to go on a date with him.
我要問你一件事
Really? Because I could kind of use the money.
真的嗎？因為我真的很缺錢
No. Joey, just, just...
走著瞧吧
He's new in town, and I know he doesn't have any guy friends.
他剛搬到這裡來 我知道他沒有男性朋友
Just take him to, like, a ballgame or something.
帶他去看球賽或做別的事 我會非常感激你
I'd really appreciate it.
好吧，我願意
Yeah, okay, sure, no problem.
-好的，沒問題 -謝謝你
Ooh, hey, donuts.
是甜甜圈
Yeah.
對
You got a red shirt?
我的天啊 這就是我睡眼朦朧的樣子？
I know. Let's try a look
這又不是俱樂部
A far-off wonderment.
出神的表情
Okay, we'll gaze into our future,
本集播出：訂婚照
and we'll think about our marriage and the days to come.
凝視我們的未來 想想我們的婚姻跟以後的日子
Chandler, what is the matter with your face?
你的鞋子上為什麼會有果醬？
Wait, this picture's supposed to say
這張照片應該要表達 「蓋勒和賓府喜事」的…
Geller and Pink to be married, not
說到在床上很自私 惠特妮還好嗎？
local woman saves drowning moron.
不是「英勇女市民 救了快淹死的混蛋」
Hey, don't laugh at him.
嘿，別笑他 這個快淹死的混蛋是我的
He's my drowning moron.
謝謝你的警告
That's it, that's it, take it, take it.
對了，就是這樣 快拍下來
I like this one. It seems to say
我喜歡這一張
I love you, and that's why I have to kill you.
它似乎是在說：「我愛你 所以我要殺了你」
It can't all be bad.
不會全部都那麼糟糕啦
Find the one where you make your bedroom eyes.
找那張你裝出 睡眼朦朧的照片
Oh, there it is.
我找到了
Oh, my God, those are my bedroom eyes?
我知道那真的很無聊 但這些票是我的老闆…
Why did you ever sleep with me?
你為什麼要跟我同床共枕？
Do you really want to pull at that thread?
你真的想提這件事情嗎？
I'm having a really good time.
-我真的玩得很開心 -我也是
Me too. Sorry that guy in the subway licked your neck.
很抱歉地鐵裡那個傢伙 舔了你的脖子
Oh.
一件
No, that's okay, he's a friend.
不，沒關係，他是我們的朋友
Hey, uh, I don't mean to be presumptuous,
恕我放肆…
but I have these two tickets to the ballroom dancing finals tomorrow night if you want to go.
但我有明天 國際標準舞總決賽的門票
Yeah, I...
對，我…
Well, you know, I mean, I missed the semifinals,
我沒有看準決賽 我想我會看不懂
so I think I would just be lost.
我想有那個可能
Look, I know that it's really lame,
不，我們坐下來長談
but I got these tickets from my boss, and...
好吧，但我有兩張 國際標準舞總決賽的門票
Oh, no, no, no, my God.
喔，不，我的天啊
Okay, don't freak out, I'll go.
好了，別大驚小怪，我去就是
No, it's... My ex-wife Whitney is out there.
是我的前妻惠特妮
I cannot deal with her right now. That woman is crazy.
我現在沒辦法面對她 那個女人瘋了
Okay, I know. Hold on.
好吧，我知道，等一下
Hey, Ross. Yeah, yeah.
-嘿，羅斯 -什麼事？
Um, that's Whitney, Kyle's ex-wife out there.
凱爾的前妻惠特妮就在外面
Now, do you think you could, you know, divert her so we could slip out?
你可以把她誘開 讓我們脫身嗎？
What? No.
什麼？不
Well, okay, but I have two tickets to the ballroom dance finals.
對，好吧，首先 你得裝出自然的樣子
Look, I don't think so, Pheebs.
我想還是不要吧，菲比
All right, I'll do it.
好吧，那麼我就安心了
But just because you're a friend.
-但那只是因為你是我的朋友 -好吧
Oh!
我的天啊
Hi, Ginger.
嗨，大舞王
All right, I want my key back.
我要拿回我的鑰匙
I don't have it.
我們不必想像
It's right there.
我在這裡耶
Ugh, okay, Sherlock.
好吧，大偵探福爾摩斯
I'm sorry, but you better go, Pheebs.
對不起 但你最好快點離開，菲比
All right, well, I just wanted to say thank you, though,
我只是要謝謝你 幫我們誘開凱爾的前妻
for diverting Kyle's ex.
如果另一個人知道 哪裡是哪裡
Oh, yeah, no, you're welcome. We'll talk about it later.
別客氣，待會再談
Okay.
好吧
Hi, Whitney.
-嗨，惠特妮 -嗨，羅斯
Hi, Ross.
他的確知道
You ready for breakfast?
-你準備好要去吃早餐了嗎？ -是的
Yep.
對
Kyle's ex-wife? You were supposed to divert her, not date her.
凱爾的前妻？你應該要誘開她 不是跟她約會
Hi, I'm sorry, can you give me a second while I talk to this woman
你能不能等我一下？ 我得跟這個女人談一談…
who, by the way, did not spend the night?
而且，她沒有在這裡過夜
Sure.
-沒問題 -好吧
Okay.
十件，好吧
I did divert her, and we ended up having a great time, okay?
我的確誘開她了 後來我們玩得很開心，好嗎？
Watching ballroom dancing?
你們一起去看標準舞比賽？
Yes, that's where we realize we are both super cool people.
對，那時我們發現 事實上我們都酷呆了
Well, look, okay, Ross,
-試著表現出性感的樣子 -好吧
Kyle just told me some really bad stuff about her.
聽著，凱爾告訴我 她有些很差勁的缺點
Like what?
譬如說呢？
Like she's really mean, and she's overly critical,
譬如說她很無情 她喜歡吹毛求疵…
and, no, she will paint a room a really bright color
她會不經過你的同意 把房間漆成很明亮的顏色
without even checking with you.
大家快來看
Okay.
低頭
And she uses sex as a weapon.
她還會把性當成武器
Fine, thank you for warning me.
對，你很高興教他怎麼當「喬伊」
At breakfast, I'll be on full alert for room painting and sex weapons.
吃早餐時我會注意 油漆跟性武器
You're still going to go out with her?
-你還是要跟她約會？ -對
Yeah.
對，當然
Well, didn't you hear what I just said?
我們剛認識時 你暗戀過我嗎？
Pheebs, come on.
菲比，少來了 你的消息來源有問題
I mean, consider the source.
聽著，你只聽到片面之詞，好嗎？
Of course her ex-husband's going to say that stuff.
她的前夫當然會那麼說 請你離開了啦
Now, if you'll excuse me.
我應該會談上一陣子，對不起
No, listen to me. She is crazy.
聽我說，她瘋了
Uh, your door isn't soundproof.
你的門沒有隔音功能
You see?
難道你們就是看不到我嗎？
Nothing is good enough for her.
看到了吧？她就是愛挑剔
Excuse me.
我們很抱歉
Daddy is not here!
我還在這裡耶
My God!
「我」會去
Do you people have nothing better to do
你相信我們都在尋找另一半嗎？
than to traipse into my office and just gawk at my assistant?
他對每一份樣本的反應是 「我一點都不在乎」
I'm Emily from upstairs.
我開始相信了
Susan's still in the hospital,
是因為我們還對彼此有感覺
and I'm collecting money to send her flowers.
很抱歉讓你們看這一幕
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
對不起
Okay. Yes, of course.
-你沒事吧？ -沒事，喬伊說我需要放輕鬆
Just take it all. Take it all.
那不是真正的我
And please, please give my best to Emily.
我們回憶了一些往事
I'm Emily.
我要娶她
Yeah, no, I meant...
對，這是瑞秋要給你的
the other one that you said.
-嘿，你來了 -我來了
Morning.
-早安 -嗨，泰格
Hi, Tag.
-嗨 -嗨
Hey, so did you have fun with, uh, with Joey last night?
聽說昨晚你跟泰格玩得很開心
Oh, yeah. We went to the Knicks game.
-昨晚你跟喬伊玩得開心嗎？ -對，我們去看尼克隊比賽
Oh, that's nice.
那真的太棒了
And then we went out to this bar,
我以前沒辦法 在酒吧裡跟女人聊天…
and he hooked us up with all these women.
然後我們去酒吧玩 他幫我們泡上好多女人
Women?
你好嗎？
You mean, like, like old women?
女人？你是說老女人？
Kind of old. Like 30.
有點老，大概三十歲
Oh.
所以…
And I never used to be able to just talk to girls in bars,
對，我根本一點都不在乎
but I got, like, 20 phone numbers last night.
但昨晚我就拿到了 二十個電話號碼
That's great.
那真的是太棒了
Oh, man.
大部份啦
So Joey must have really taught you some stuff, huh?
喬伊真的教會你一些事
A little.
沒錯
Yeah.
對，那傢伙還不錯
How you doing?
你在想什麼？
See?
寵愛？
That's a great smile.
看吧？那個笑容非常燦爛 放輕鬆，自然一點
Easy, natural.
我們要再試一次
Now pretend I have a camera.
現在假裝我手上拿了照相機
You're changing it.
-你的笑容變了 -我控制不了自己
I can't help it.
-早安，瑞秋 -嗨
All right, all right, all right, all right.
我常常這樣暗戀男人 剛認識你時我就暗戀過你
You want to know what I do when I take resume shots?
你想知道 我都是怎麼拍沙龍照的嗎？
Borrow money from me?
你跟我借錢？
Yeah.
我們得走了
Okay.
低頭
First of all, you want to make it look spontaneous, right?
不，你不能搶走他
Okay, so here's what I do.
好了，看吧，低頭
I look down.
然後抬頭
Look down.
我會努力調整自己
Keep looking down.
低頭，低頭，繼續低頭
Then I look up.
當我談戀愛時
See?
喂？
All right, now you try.
看到沒？現在你來試試看
Look down.
我吃了甜甜圈
You're looking down.
剛剛你說 「我一直都很快樂，當…」
Keep looking down.
我都是這麼做的，我會低頭 低頭，繼續低頭
Why is there jelly on your shoe?
但這真的讓我很困擾，好嗎？
I had a donut.
你還想怎麼樣？
Hi.
對，我…
Hey.
拿去吧
Hey, so, uh, heard you had some fun with Tag last night.
你得原諒她 知道該怎麼面對她的生活
Yeah, that guy's all right.
我的背真的好痛
Yeah, and you had fun teaching him how to be all...
-對，我們是天生一對 -一點都沒錯
Joey.
-我跟喬伊出去 -是嗎？
What?
什麼？
You know, all the women.
-什麼？ -你知道的，泡馬子
Hey, hey, you can't teach someone to be good with women.
你沒辦法教別人怎麼泡馬子
Huh?
什麼？
That's why I never had any luck with Chandler.
所以我跟錢德出去 老是泡不到馬子
I'm right here.
-我沒拿 -鑰匙就那裡
All right, well, would you mind just not going out with him again?
你在暗戀他 為什麼還要僱用他？
Okay, just the idea of you and he and all these women and it just...
就是你跟他一起去泡馬子…
And I know he's my assistant and I can't date him, blah, blah, blah.
我知道他是我的助理 我不能跟他約會
But I just... It bothers me, all right?
每晚把公事帶回家做 或許他就不會那樣子
No, no, no, no.
我們也是
You can't take him away from me.
你有事要跟我談？
I got a great partner to pick up girls with.
我終於找到一個 可以跟我一起去泡馬子的拍檔
Finally.
我知道，摩妮卡跟我說過
I'm still right here.
威利還活著
All right, well, will you at least talk to him
你能跟他談談嗎？
and tell him how hollow and unsatisfying
告訴他跟一大堆女人約會 既空虛又得不到滿足
this dating tons of women thing is?
如果那個人已經出現在你的生命中 你應該努力去爭取嗎？
What?
什麼？
I just don't want him to meet anybody until I'm over my crush.
在我結束對他的暗戀之前 我不要他跟任何人約會
And I will get over it.
至少你可以跟他談一談…
It's not like I love him. It's just physical.
我並不愛他 那只是肉體上的吸引力
But, you know, I mean, I get crushes like this all the time.
-我知道 -所以他都尿不准，但那不重要
I mean, Al, I had a crush on you when I first met you.
我搭地鐵時睡著了 結果到了布魯克林
I know. Monica told me.
我們得談一談
Did you have a crush on me when you first met me?
他做其他事時，也會哼歌
Yeah, sure.
-真的嗎？ -對你來說是的
Can you people not see me?
我不知道 你拿了東西來給我嗎？
So, will you talk to him?
我可以好好寵愛她
I don't know, Rach.
-我不知道，瑞秋 -我會送你十件勞夫羅蘭的襯衫
Oh, come on. I'll give you ten free Ralph Lauren shirts.
我想我不會 再去酒吧泡女人了
One.
一件
No, ten. You said ten. You can't take that back.
不，十件，你說十件 你不能反悔
Hey, Joey. You wanted to talk to me?
之後她才動手漆房間
I don't know. You got something for me?
-你不會關心這種事 -不，我很關心
Oh, yeah. This is from Rachel.
-看起來不錯 -你們看起來很配
Ten.
十件，好吧
Okay.
我能下場打球嗎？
Now, Tag, there's such a thing as too many women.
泰格，跟太多女人約會 是不好的
Really?
-錢德 -什麼事？
Yeah, for you.
如果她沒有…
Hey.
拿去吧
Hey, how much would it cost to get a big fan in here?
菲比，你沒有看錯她
Hey, there you are.
兄弟，那一記反手投籃帥呆了
There I am.
兄弟，那太慘了
You okay?
你認為他吝於付出感情？
Yeah, Joey said I needed to relax,
喔，快說吧，凱爾
so he gave me an antihistamine.
他給我吃抗組胺藥
What?
什麼？
Yeah, and then I fell asleep on the subway
你們又去泡妞了？
and went all the way to Brooklyn.
我們明白 我們會這麼氣對方…
Brooklyn is far.
布魯克林好遠
Chandler, what were you thinking?
-錢德，你覺得呢？ -沒問題，但我不去
No, no, but don't worry, don't worry,
別擔心 因為現在我知道要怎麼拍照了
because I know how to take a picture now.
她的確試圖把性當成武器
Okay, see? Look down.
我沒想到你會那麼說
Look down.
低頭
Chandler?
-錢德 -什麼事？
Yeah?
對
Hi.
對，我…
So, how are things going with Krazy?
你跟瘋婆子還好吧？ 她把你的兔子拿去煮了嗎？
Has she cooked your rabbit yet?
對，因為你很善變
Listen, you are hearing one side of the story, okay?
如果他正在辦離婚 你覺得跟他約會適當嗎？
And FYI, she must have shown Kyle over 30 paint samples
還有，她拿了三十份 油漆樣本給凱爾看…
before she painted that room.
沒有他們，我們能過得更好
And his response to each one was,
或許她不必在床上很自私…
I don't give a tiny rat's ass.
我們要找回六年的時光
Yeah, well, maybe she should have spent
或許她該少花點時間在裝潢上…
a little less time decorating
對不起，吵到你了嗎？
and a little more time in the bedroom.
-我媽把報紙寄給我 -我們來瞧瞧
Well, I don't think we are gonna have that problem,
你們為什麼不請專業攝影師 幫你們拍照呢？
but maybe that's just because
但或許那是因為 我不會吝於付出感情
I am not emotionally unavailable.
想像一下我們的孩子會是什麼模樣
You think he's emotionally unavailable?
-你們在做什麼？ -我媽打電話來
I think he can be.
你知道的，他會邊尿邊哼歌
Well, maybe he wouldn't be
幾乎談了一整個晚上…
if she didn't bring the office home with her every night.
她的確知道 她在1997年除夕做了什麼
Well, excuse her for knowing
昨晚我到凱爾家 拿一些東西…
what she wants to do with her life.
你不是說她愛抱怨 常常要人注意她嗎？
Yeah, well, she certainly knew
那是三年前的事 她一再地道歉
what she was doing New Year's Eve, 1997.
她的確知道 她在1997年除夕做了什麼
I knew you were gonna throw that in my face!
-你們兩個在一起？ -怎麼了？
That was three years ago.
那是三年前的事 她一再地道歉
She apologized and apologized.
-我喜歡女朋友陪在身邊 -真的嗎？
What more do you want?
你還想怎麼樣？
We want the last six years back!
就算他們再分手，千萬別讓他 加入你的傷心男子俱樂部
So do we! So do we!
我們也是
I'm sorry you had to see that.
-是離婚男人俱樂部 -有什麼不一樣呢
Morning, Rachel.
-嗨，瑞秋 -嗨，梅麗莎，有什麼事嗎？
Hi.
對，我…
Hey, so, uh, what'd you do last night?
昨晚你做了什麼？
Went out with Joey.
-我要跟我前女友復合 -我願意
Oh, yeah?
-不 -沒錯
Another night of bird-dogging the chicas?
我一直都很快樂，當… 我為什麼要告訴你這件事？
No.
還是不要吧
We had a really good talk.
不，我們坐下來長談
Oh.
一件
I don't think I'm gonna do that bar scene anymore.
我想我不會 再去酒吧泡女人了
Wow.
哇。
I did not see that coming.
我沒想到你會那麼說
That's just not really who I am.
那不是真正的我
You know, I've always been happier when...
我一直都很快樂，當… 我為什麼要告訴你這件事？
Why am I telling you this?
你的鞋子上為什麼會有果醬？
You don't care about this stuff.
-你不會關心這種事 -不，我很關心
No, yes, I do, I do, I do.
應該沒有，喬伊
I mean...
我是說…
Come on, go on.
來吧，繼續說。
You were saying I'm happier when I'm, you know...
剛剛你說 「我一直都很快樂，當…」
When I'm in a relationship.
當我談戀愛時
I love having a girlfriend.
-我喜歡女朋友陪在身邊 -真的嗎？
Really?
喂？
Yeah, someone I can spoil, you know?
我可以好好寵愛她
Spoil?
寵愛？
Let me ask you something.
我要問你一件事
Uh-huh?
嗯？
Do you believe there's one perfect person for everyone?
你相信我們都在尋找另一半嗎？
I'm starting to.
我開始相信了
And if that person's already in your life,
如果那個人已經出現在你的生命中 你應該努力去爭取嗎？
you should do something about it, right?
你能不能別再跟他一起出去？
Yes, hell yes.
對，當然
All right, then, it's settled.
好吧，那麼我就安心了
Okay.
好吧
I'm getting back together with my ex-girlfriend.
-我要跟我前女友復合 -我願意
I would love to.
我會忘記他的
Huh?
什麼？
Hello?
喂？
Oh, yeah, this is gonna be a while.
我應該會談上一陣子，對不起
Excuse me.
對不起。
Um...
所以…
Yeah.
對
Yeah!
My God!
我的天啊
Oh, I'm sorry.
對不起
Is that annoying?
對不起，吵到你了嗎？
Oh, and speaking of being selfish in bed,
說到在床上很自私 惠特妮還好嗎？
how's Whitney?
他不在，怎麼了？
Well, maybe she wouldn't have to be selfish in bed
或許她不必在床上很自私…
if someone else knew where everything was.
如果另一個人知道 哪裡是哪裡
Oh, he knows.
他的確知道
For the most part.
大部份啦
Oh, hey.
他的確知道
Good, you're both here.
嘿，太好了，你們兩個都在
We kind of need to talk.
我們得談一談
Both of you together?
-你們兩個在一起？ -怎麼了？
What's up?
什麼？
Well, I went over to Kyle's last night
昨晚我到凱爾家 拿一些東西…
to pick up a few things,
and we got to reminiscing.
我們回憶了一些往事
We talked through most of the night,
幾乎談了一整個晚上…
and we realized that the reason we're so angry with each other
我們明白 我們會這麼氣對方…
is because there are still feelings there.
是因為我們還對彼此有感覺
So...
所以…
Oh, just say it, Kyle!
喔，快說吧，凱爾
We're gonna give it another try.
我們要再試一次
What about her whining
你在想什麼？
and her constant need for attention?
你不是說她愛抱怨 常常要人注意她嗎？
I'm gonna work on that.
我會努力調整自己
Oh, right.
對，那傢伙還不錯
Because you're so capable of change.
對，因為你很善變
You know, he hums when he pees.
你知道的，他會邊尿邊哼歌
I do know.
他的確知道
Makes him miss the bowl, but whatever.
-我知道 -所以他都尿不准，但那不重要
We're so sorry.
我們很抱歉
That's all right.
對，那傢伙還不錯
We don't need you, all right?
我們得談一談
In fact, hey, I'm over it already.
沒關係，我們不需要你們 我已經忘了這件事
Yeah, and you know what?
羅斯，或許你認識他
I don't even give a tiny rat's ass.
對，我根本一點都不在乎
Yeah, we're gonna go.
我們得走了
I'm sorry.
對不起
Pheebs, you were right about her.
菲比，你沒有看錯她
You know, she did try to use sex as a weapon.
她的確試圖把性當成武器
Yeah, it hurt my back a little.
我的背真的好痛
You know, he hums while he does other stuff, too.
他做其他事時，也會哼歌
Yeah, we're better off without them.
沒有他們，我們能過得更好
And you know, even if they break up again,
-什麼？ -你知道的，泡馬子
you better not let him in your sad men's club.
就算他們再分手，千萬別讓他 加入你的傷心男子俱樂部
Divorced men's club.
或許我該成立 一個離婚男子俱樂部
Potato, potatoe.
番茄，蕃茄。
You know, Pheebs, we don't talk that much anymore.
我想我不會 再去酒吧泡女人了
Yeah.
對
Hey, guys, check it out.
大家快來看
My mom sent me the paper.
-我媽把報紙寄給我 -我們來瞧瞧
Oh, let's see it.
對，那傢伙還不錯
Oh, yeah, that looks good.
-看起來不錯 -你們看起來很配
You guys make a very attractive couple.
Yeah, we look great together.
-對，我們是天生一對 -一點都沒錯
We really do.
不，我們坐下來長談
Okay.
好吧
Wow, imagine what our kids would look like.
想像一下我們的孩子會是什麼模樣
You know, we don't have to imagine.
我們不必想像
I'm marrying her.
我要娶她
We'll just see.
走著瞧吧